Xiaofeng
小枫啊
Let you sit in this position
让你坐这个位置
It is we who give Lao Xu a face
是我们给老徐总的一个面子
You do things like this
你这样做事
It makes it difficult for me
让我很难办
I'm already investigating
我已经在调查了
I can assure you
我敢保证
This plan must belong to our company
这个方案一定是我们公司的
I won't make it difficult for our company
我不会让我们公司难办
No, someone has already taken care of the other company
不用了已经有人把对方公司搞定了
And after our board of directors studied it,
而且经过我们董事会研究
He is better suited to sit in this position than you are
他比你更适合坐在这个位置
Xiaofeng, we are not forcing you
小枫啊我们也不是逼你
But I hope you
而是希望你呢
Make a good decision for everyone by yourself
自己做出一个对大家都好的决定
Someone took care of the other company
有人把对方公司搞定了
But her designs are all in the company's encrypted data
但她的设计方案都在公司加密资料里
These are her painstaking efforts and belong to her
这些都是她的心血领属于她
You sign this
你在这上面签个字
I'll help you settle all this down
我帮你安顿好这一切
Nanfeng
楠枫
It is also a child I brought up since I was a child
也是我从小带大的孩子
Why would he do this to us
他为什么要这样对我们
Xiaofeng
小枫啊
Ever since you were removed from the board of directors,
自从你被董事会除名以后
The only one who can help us now is the Chen family
现在能帮我们的只有陈家了
This is the last hope of our Xu family
这可是我们徐家最后的希望
You can't be willful any longer
你可不能再任性了
Why
为什么
Do you remember
你还记得
Did I tell you about the car accident
我跟你说过的车祸吗
I thought you said
你不是说
Was that an accident
那是场意外吗
Since it was an accident,
既然是意外
Why don't you show me the accident replay
为什么不给我看事故回放
Why shattered glass
为什么要欲盖弥彰
But they also adopted you
可是他们还收养了你
How could it hurt your father
怎么可能害你爸爸
Then why is only my dad dead
那为什么只有我爸死了
My world has collapsed
我的世界已经崩塌了
They sneezed like they did
他们却像打了个喷嚏一样
Besides, they adopted me
何况他们收养我
It's just for business image
也只是为了商业形象
From small to large
从小到大
I'm just a tool man for my brother's feet
我都只是给我弟垫脚的工具人而已
But you still call him brother
可你还叫他弟弟
It's just a habit
那只是习惯
So
所以
All of it
所有的一切
It's all fake, isn't it
都是假的是吗
To you
对你
No
不是
Actually, I have something to say to you today
其实我今天是有话要对你说
I have something to say to you, too
我也有话要对你说
Ah
啊
Listen to the opinions of the directors
听听各位董事的意见吧
Now the other company has something on us
现在对方公司捏住了我们的把柄
Even bear legal responsibility
甚至还要负法律责任
Xiaofeng
小枫啊
You have to shoulder the heavy responsibility at this critical moment
在这个关键时刻你要担起重任
It is also an explanation for these antiques
也是给我们这几个古董一个交代
Everyone said, right
大家说是吧
Members of the Directors
各位董事
This is
这里是
All drafts of design scheme and design process
设计方案的全部草稿和设计流程
And the proofreading time of each edition
以及各个版本的校备时间
With this evidence,
有了这个证据
Who did what behind his back
是谁在背后做了什么
I believe the relevant departments will find out soon
相信有关部门很快就能查出来
What's going on here
这怎么回事
It's too late to explain
来不及解释了
He needs your help
他需要你的帮助
My family can only help drag it off for a while
我家也只能帮忙拖一阵子了
I thought this manuscript was damaged
本来我以为这个原稿被损坏了
Actually, it was transferred
其实是被人转移了
This man is
这个人就是
Who is this man
这个人是谁
I believe Mr. Xu will find out
相信徐先生会查出来
Give the directors an account
给各位董事一个交代的
Telephone supplement: Didn't you say that the Xu family is foolproof
电话补录：你不是说搞徐家万无一失吗
Telephone supplement: Now we are the defendant's side instead
电话补录：现在我们反而成为了被告的一方
Telephone supplement: I tell you I'm not finished with you about this
电话补录：我告诉你 这事我跟你没完
I'm sorry
对不起
You don't hate me
你不恨我
Do you know why I chose to return home to inherit my family property
知道我为什么选择回国继承家产吗
It's not because I can't get along outside
不是因为在外面混不下去了
I can only go home and inherit hundreds of millions of possessions
只能回家继承亿万家产
Because when I was little, someone told me
是因为我小的时候有人告诉我
Will always support me to realize my dream
会一直支持我实现自己的梦想
Thank you for coming back.
谢谢你还愿意回来
Are you still leaving
你还要走吗
Hello
喂
What happened to my mother
我妈怎么了
Now
现在
But it will take me three hours to get back at the earliest
可是我最快也要3个小时才能回去啊
Okay, I'll find a way. Don't worry
好好我想办法你别急
3 hours
3个小时